CHUCK FLORES

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

I aim to design equally intuitive and engaging user-centered apps, websites, and solutions. My process combines the analytical, technical, and artistic aspects from my previous experience in music and design. I turn ideas into reality.

UX Skills



Experience



Research

Competitor Analysis

Layout Analysis

User Interviews

User Journeys

Persona Distillation

User Flows

Information Architecture

Sitemaps

Card Sorting

Page Templates

Design

Sketching

Task Analysis

Wireframing

User Interface Design

High Fidelity Mock Ups

Testing

Usability Testing Rapid Prototyping

UX Designer - OkMyOutfit

May 2015

- Analyze and investigate areas of improvement for professional styling website
- Redesign home page to provide clear communication to viewers
- Modify on-boarding process to increase visitor conversion
- Perform usability tests and iterate on Style Profile designs

UX Designer - Trail Brief App

April 2015

- Create and design a trail info app for hikers
- Interview hikers to determine needs and features
- Prepare detailed research report and planning documentation
- Run usability tests and iterate on designs, resulting in a hi-fi prototype

Freelance Audio Engineer - C&C Music Factory

March 2009 - March 2015

March 2015 - May 2015

January 2015 - May 2015

- Track and mix music sessions with producer
- Design and code artist websites
- Upload and maintain music for online distribution through multiple platforms
- Instruct production team on Pro Tools / Logic software

Tools



Education



Sketch 3

OmniGraffle

Photoshop

InVision

P.O.P Prototyping

Hype 3

HTML / CSS / SASS

Typeform

Dropbox

Trello

portfolio: chuckflores.com

User Experience Design Immersive General Assembly - New York, NY

Graphic Design & Typography School of Visual Arts - New York, NY

Bachelor of Science in Music Business Full Sail University - Orlando, FL

Associate of Science in Recording Arts

Full Sail University - Orlando, FL

chuck.e.flores@gmail.com

September 2007 - October 2008

January 2009 - October 2009

540-907-2101

87 Eagle St, Brooklyn, NY